http://www.rohwrestling.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Sign In
Cart(0)
Introduction
You have entered a website owned and operated by, or on behalf of, Ring of Honor Wrestling Entertainment, LLC and/or its affiliated companies (“ROH”). Your use of our Website means that you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into and forms a part of the Website’s terms and conditions (set forth in _________).
This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision at our discretion. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Personal Information (as described below), such changes will be posted on the Website. If you object to any such changes, you must stop using the Website. Continued use of the Website following notice of any changes indicates your agreement to them.
ROH wants you to enjoy your visit to our Website but also help protect your personal privacy while you are visiting and afterwards. Most of your visits to our Website will not involve collection of any of your Personal Information. There are areas of our Website which involve membership or a registration process where you will need to submit personal information such as your name, address, date of birth, contact information, payment information, phone number, etc. (“Personal Information”).
The Personal Information we collect depends on what you do when you visit our Website or use the various products or services we offer. By using our Website, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any terms or practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Website.
Special Note About Children
Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. ROH is also committed to fully complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ( "COPPA"). Our protections for the privacy of children include the following:
We do not knowingly solicit, collect, use, disclose or retain any Personal Information, for any purpose whatsoever (including internal or external marketing or promotional purposes), from visitors to our Website who are age 13 or younger. In addition, we will delete any records of such Personal Information that come to our attention. BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ARE REPRESENTING THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST 13 YEARS OLD.
We do not allow visitors who are age 13 or younger to be listed in any directory of registered users, to participate in any of our chat services, to register for contests, sweepstakes, promotions, or newsletters or to receive direct marketing from us or from our third-party affiliates or service or product providers.
Special Note to Parents
If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, we invite you to contact us so that we may delete the information from our records and discontinue any related features or services.
Collection of Personal Information
ROH collects Personal Information from visitors to our Website in a number of ways. These include:
Subscriptions to our free newsletters, which include updates, special offers and promotions from ROH.
Participation in contests and sweepstakes.
Registrations to receive free downloadable desktop applications (e.g., screensavers).
Registrations to participate in chat services, forums and social media interaction.
Registrations for myROH and use of standard or premium membership features.
Purchases of merchandise, Streaming Pay Per View events, and transactions where home delivery is required.
E-mail transmitted via various links on our web sites.
The use of any of these services is entirely optional and voluntary. Please be aware that sending your Personal Information by email is not a secure method of transmission; so, in particular, you should not transmit any credit card information by email.
Cookies
Like most major websites, our website uses “cookies”. A “cookie” is a small piece of text that a web server stores in your computer in order to make your experience better upon return visits to the website. These pieces of information that are sent by websites and stored in your computer's hard drive allow websites to recognize your computer so that you do not have to re-enter the same data every time you visit that website. They also allow websites to learn how visitors use the websites. Aggregated usage data enables us to tailor our content to our visitors' interests and to help our advertisers better understand the preferences of our audience. Providing such usage data to advertisers is essential to keeping as many of our services free to visitors as is reasonably possible. This information does not reveal your identity although, in some cases, we may have to combine this non-identifiable information with Personal Information to protect our services, Website, visitors or others.
Promotional Offers
From time to time, we might send you offers from us or one of our business affiliates or partners. When we do this, we do not share your Personal Information with our business affiliates/partners. If you do not wish to receive such offers, please contact us at the email shown below.
Visitors From Outside the United States
All Personal Information collected at our Website is collected and stored in the United States (U.S.). By using our Website and/or by submitting Personal Information to our Website, you consent to having your information transferred to the U.S. and being processed and maintained in the U.S., subject to applicable U.S. laws.
How We Use Your Personal Information
We limit the manner in which your Personal Information is used. We will use the Personal Information you provide only in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. We use Personal Information to: provide you the products and services you want; administer or enforce transactions you have requested; protect your accounts from fraud, unauthorized access or identity theft; verify your identity in connection with transactions you have requested; and to manage our business and protect our interests. We also use Personal Information to better understand and serve the needs of our Website visitors, and to provide news and information on new content, products services, and features of our Website via direct e-mail.
We may share Personal Information with our service providers to assist us with any of the purposes set forth above (which, for example, might include disclosures to attorneys, accountants, auditors, credit bureaus, data processors and technical systems consultants) but only to the extent necessary or appropriate for them to perform their services for us. Please note that we will release your Personal Information if required to do so by law, search warrant, subpoena, court order or other legal process.
We do not otherwise sell or provide your Personal Information to third parties.
Links to Third Party Web Sites
This Privacy Policy applies only to our ROH website. Our Website may contain certain hyperlinks to other websites, some of which may display ROH logos or other ROH content. These websites may have privacy policies; however, all of these websites and their privacy policies are independent of our Website or this Privacy Policy. ROH is not responsible for compliance with other websites' privacy policies or data collection practices. You should review these privacy policies carefully before providing any Personal Information to these websites.
Third Party Ad Servers
Ads appearing on our Website may be delivered to you by third party advertising companies. Information about your visits to our Website, such as the number of times you have viewed one of our advertisements, the date/time at which the ads were shown, the advertisers' cookies, and the IP address of the computer you use (but not your address or other Personal Information) is used to make sure that our ads are helpful to you. We do not have access to the cookies that may be placed by our third party advertising companies. We share usage information about visitors to our Website with these companies for the purposes of managing and targeting advertisements, measuring their effectiveness, and for market research analysis.
Limitations on Use of Personal Information
We will use or retain your Personal Information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, and only for so long as is needed to fulfill your requests, support the services you have requested, process your orders, or comply with the law. When you make a purchase, sign up for a paid service, we will also collect your credit card information as additional Personal Information. We will use this credit card information only to complete the specific transaction(s) you have requested. We do not store your credit card information or keep, use, or maintain it for any reason other than the processing of individual transactions. For each new transaction that requires credit card information, you will need to give us your credit card information each time.
Security of Personal Information
Our Website has put in place reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of your Personal Information and we use reasonable precautions to protect it from loss, misuse and alteration. We use encryption software when dealing with certain information such as credit card numbers, etc. Only our employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Please note, however, if you choose to post your Personal Information on chat rooms, forums and message boards, it will be publicly available and you should have no expectation of privacy or security with respect to such information.
Opt-Out
Any feature on our Website requiring registration allows you to opt-out from receiving any newsletters, product offers, or other correspondence from either us or our business affiliates. In addition, if after registering, you would no longer like to receive any such materials or correspondence, send an e-mail to help@rohwrestling.com. Indicate your preference to "unsubscribe, " and we will promptly remove you from our list. Please be sure to include your name and e-mail address in the e-mail. You will need to send separate e-mails if you are registered for more than one of our features or services.
Violation of These Terms of Use
ROH may disclose and/or preserve any Personal Information if we determine that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of our Website, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, or the rights or property of our Website’s users. ROH reserves the right at all times to disclose any Personal Information that we deem necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, fraud investigation or governmental request.
You agree that ROH may, in its sole discretion and without prior notice, terminate your access to our Website, for cause, which includes (but is not limited to) (1) requests by law enforcement or other government agencies, (2) a request by you (self-initiated account deletions), (3) discontinuance or material modification of our Website or any service offered on or through our Website, or (4) unexpected technical issues or problems.
Void Where Prohibited
Although our Website is accessible worldwide, not all features, products or services discussed, referenced, provided or offered through or on the Website are available to all persons or in all geographic locations, or appropriate or available for use outside the United States. ROH reserves the right to limit, in its sole discretion, the provision and quantity of any feature, product or service to any person or geographic area. Any offer for any feature, product or service made on our Website is void where prohibited. If you choose to access our Website from outside the United States, you do so voluntarily and you are solely responsible for complying for the laws where you are located.
Contact Us
If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy, or wish to lodge a complaint about any conduct that you believe is not consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to the following address:
Help@rohwrestling.com
Experience
Buy Tickets
HonorClub Membership
Upcoming Events
Past Events
Watch
Pay Per View
© 2020 Ring of Honor Wrestling Entertainment, LLC. All Rights Reserved | Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
